<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Railway Secuirty | Home</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tag/railway-secuirty/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/tag/railway-secuirty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Railway Secuirty</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hud9e2f43ab6f21cec988f7b26ad197544_2176_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Railway Secuirty</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tag/railway-secuirty/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formal modeling of moving block signaling system</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/project/formal-modeling-of-moving-block-signaling-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/project/formal-modeling-of-moving-block-signaling-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A subsystem of the ERTMS/ETCS Level 3 moving block architecture
is a typical example of a NCS. The system aims at controlling trains’
movement by using as few trackside devices as possible and relying on direct
communication with trains. Radio-block centers (RBC) are deployed to deliver
signals to trains and receive feedback. Each RBC controls the movement of the
trains along a certain area by either authorizing them to move at a certain speed
or stopping them. RBC sends to a train, passing through its area, a movement
authority – a message containing among others danger point and end of the
movement authority (EoA). A train is not allowed to pass its EoA to avoid hazardous
situations. However, depending on the implementation, a safety margin
might define a danger point to be beyond EoA. Therefore, the safety property
usually is defined in terms of not passing the danger point, although, according
to the definition, the train must not pass its EoA. In this project, we
prove the safety property while the communication channel between the train
and RBC is under attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We consider an attacker who performs a two-phase attack. First, she injects
a valid movement authority message to set the value of EoA beyond the danger
point defined by RBC. Such an attack constitutes a direct safety hazard since
the EOA set by the attacker could be at the rear end of another train.
Therefore, the train accepts the forged message. In the second phase, the attacker
actively monitors train-RBC communication and takes some actions e.g.,
dropping a message to prevent the detection of the attack and stopping the train
before passing the intended EoA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We model and analyze the communication between RBC and
the train to derive necessary and sufficient conditions that
guarantee safety in the presence of the attacker.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
